<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Execute TestCases">
   <intro>
   <description>
     In a few steps, this cheat sheet will guide you through the execution of TestCases and evaluation of the respective results.
     You will need a card reader and an ePassport. You can also use an nPA, but then switch any
     statements regarding nPA with ePassport and vice-versa.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Setup Test Environment">
      <description>
         Make sure your card reader is connected to you computer. First, do not put your ePassport on it.
         If your card reader just had to be connected, start GlobalTester 3 again.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Import your TestSpecification">
      <description>
         If not already done, import the &quot;GlobalTester Sample TestSpecification&quot;.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Create and execute TestCampaign">
      <description>
        In your &quot;GlobalTester Sample TestSpecification&quot;, select the TestCases &quot;SelectApplication_nPA.xml&quot;
        and &quot;SelectApplication_ePassport.xml&quot;.
        Right-click your mouse, and choose <b>&quot;RunTest&quot;</b>.<br/>
        A TestCampaign will be created and executed directly.
        Both TestCases will have a &quot;FAILURE&quot; - notice in their &quot;Status&quot;-column in the TestCampaign editor.
      </description>
   </item>
    <item
         title="Try to find the Error in your Log File">
      <description>
      	In the TestCampaign editor, you can see a tree view displaying the last execution of the TestCampaign structured in its TestCase and Test Steps.
        Right-click with your mouse on the root of the tree view which corresponds to the last execution of the TestCampaign,
        and choose <b>&quot;Show log file&quot;</b>.
        The log file will open. Have a close look at it.<br/>
        You can find your error in the TestCase execution by looking for &quot;@FailureID1&quot;, &quot;@FailureID2&quot;, etc.
        The lines in the  log file where they appear will have a red marker.
        If you click on it, the line where the failure is reported will open and be highlighted.<br/>
        Usually &quot;@FailureID1&quot; is the essential source of error; here it is the missing &quot;card&quot; reference
        (because you have no card placed on your reader).
      </description>
   </item>
   
   <item
         title="Execute TestCampaign with different Setup">
      <description>
      	Now put your ePassport on the card reader.
        You can (re-) execute your TestCampaign by clicking the <b>&quot;Execute&quot;</b> button.
        This time the &quot;SelectApplication_nPA&quot; execution will report a failure as well,
        but the &quot;SelectApplication_ePassport&quot; execution will be declared as &quot;PASSED&quot;.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Evaluate Log File again...">
      <description>
        Open the log file of the &quot;SelectApplication_ePassport&quot; execution.
        You can now see the communication between the card and the reader.
        The command APDU is syntax highlighted.
        When you hover over it, you can see information about the command APDU.
        The response APDU is shown as well, and its status word is extracted.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="... and again.">
      <description>
      	Open the log file of the &quot;SelectApplication_nPA&quot; execution.
        This time there is a &quot;card&quot; reference, so there is also a command APDU in the execution.
        The response APDU is only the status word &quot;6a82&quot;, because there is no nPA related eID application on your card.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Generate Report">
      <description>
        You can generate a report of your execution by clicking the <b>&quot;Generate Report&quot;</b> button.
        A folder browser will open where you can choose the folder you want the report to be saved in.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Browse TestCampaign Executions">
      <description>
         TODO
      </description>
      <onCompletion>Congratulations! You have just learned how to execute TestCases and evaluate the respective results!</onCompletion>
   </item>
   

</cheatsheet>
